backlinkbooster.com 2015-04-09

# Backlink Booster | Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**Confidentiality & Anonymity**   
As a Backlink Booster member or affiliate, we treat your privacy with the upmost respect. We do not allow search engine bots to crawl the accounts section of our website, and we do not advertise a customer list or your information as a client anyplace so your anonymity is protected.

**How We Use Information**  
When you supply us with your contact information, you may receive periodic mailings or phone calls from us with information on products and services or upcoming events. However, your information is not openly shared with other organizations for commercial purposes unless you've actively elected to have your information shared. Our privacy practices do not cover information of third-party web sites that are linked to Backlink Booster.

**Your Personal Information**  
All visitors to Backlink Booster can view our content without providing any personal information. However, in order to membership and link information, you must complete an account registration that requires you to provide your name, mailing address, phone number and email address, and we do not send your information to, or share it with, any other business, except as otherwise described in this Agreement. We store your information securely in our database and the database may be outside your home country.

You may register to receive our newsletter or to receive other forms of communications from us on a periodic basis. We do not share your name or email address with any other companies, and only use the information to provide you with the information you requested. In addition, every email we send you will include an option for you to opt-out of future emails, or you can email us at [info@BacklinkBooster.com](mailto:info@BacklinkBooster.com) to opt-out of further communications. 

Finally, you may post information and comments on the site through our forum options. Please be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in comments on our forum, and these communications are considered public and will be available for others to see. As a result, please use prudence when posting comments or opinions. If you ever post a comment you wish to have removed, please notify us and we will work with you to remove your comments from the System. 

**Our use of cookies**  
In many cases, we use "cookies" to collect and/or store non-personal information from/to your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data that a website stores on your computer's hard drive, and you can remove cookies from your hard drive. A cookie is a standard Internet technology that enables us to save your personal preferences to your computer, which helps us to provide a better user experience for you. This information cannot harm your computer in any way and does not contain personally identifiable information. Some cookies are placed on your computer while visiting our website by third-party service providers who provide us with web analytics.

Depending on your web browser, you may be able to disable cookies so we cannot save them to your computer. However, this will severely limit your ability to use our website, or our partners' websites, to request information from franchised businesses. As a result, we strongly recommend that you enable cookies in your web browser when using our website or those of our partners. 

**Information sharing**  
We may choose to share either personal or non-personal information with third-parties in order to provide a requested service or transaction. Specifically we may share your non-personal link information with other members in order to distribute your links for display on other websites in the network, and vice-versa. We also reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our company. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our site utilizes a secure socket layer (SSL) during registration, membership services, and the entire checkout process.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your account. As a result, you will be required to select and use a private password when creating and accessing your account.

**Site and Service Updates**   
On occasion, we may send site and service announcement updates to members. Our members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about Backlink Booster. We communicate with members to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

**Notification of Changes to this Privacy Policy**   
By using Backlink Booster, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on this page so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether we use their information in this different manner.

**How To Contact Us**   
Backlink Booster is owned and operated by Internet Powered Solutions LLC. If you do not wish to receive emails, mailings or phone calls, or you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at:

> Internet Powered Solutions, LLC  
>  12322 W 64th Ave, Suite 112   
>  Arvada, CO 80004

We can be reached via email at [info@BacklinkBooster.com](mailto:info@BacklinkBooster.com), or you can call us at (303) 900-1333.

_Last Updated: November 30, 2009_
